1/ Code
 - Using patterns: Strategy, Template Mehothod, Dependency Injection, SOLID.
 - Exception handling: using service messages.

2/ Answer questions
 - How accurate is the predictor?
	Compare the predicted value to the actual value to see the error between them. 
        Common usage methods: Root Mean Squared Error (RMSE), Mean Absolute Percentage Error(MAPE), Mean Absolute Scaled Error(MASE)
	* Reference: https://fairmodel.econ.yale.edu/rayfair/pdf/1984B8.PDF
                   https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC5570302/
 - How could we make it more accurate?
	In order to improve our predited value using linear regression model, we should:
	+ Collect as much sample data as possible. More is always better.
	+ Update our model to use multiple linear regression that includes multiple predictor variables.
	  Doing this by adding a slope coefficient for each additional independent variable of interest to our model.
          i.e. Currency value of a country depends on that country's gold, so just add gold exchange rate as a variable to the model, 
		then it would be: Currency exchange rate = Intercept + Slope1(Date) + Slope2(Gold exchange rate) + Error.
	
3/ Guildline
 - Folder structure
   --\bin
    \src
    \answer.readme.txt
  
 - Execute application on bin\Os.Application.exe
 - Source code from \src. All packages will be downloaded at the first time solution launched
 - The answer and guildline included in \answer.readme.txt